wdde.info 2014-09-10

# Privacy Policy | WDDE 91.1 FM | Delaware's NPR News station

**PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy describes, in general, the practices related to the online collection and use of personal information at this website. By accessing this website, you are accepting these practices.

**_Our Collection and Use of Information_**

We do not collect personal information about you on this website unless you choose to provide it, such as by registering on our website, completing an online survey, or making a donation or purchase.

To register on our website, you must provide personal information such as your name, postal and email addresses, telephone numbers, and certain demographic information. If you choose to provide us with your personal information, we will retain and may use it to contact you, to respond to your inquiries, to customize the services we provide to you, and to ensure compliance with our policies and applicable laws.

Whereas we do not collect personal information (including but not limited to your name, postal and email addresses, telephone numbers, and certain demographic information) unless you provide it when you visit our website, we may collect and store information such as the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, the kind of browser software and operating system you are using, the date and time you access our website, the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our website, and other such information.  Like most website operators, we use cookies, web beacons, log files, and other electronic information collection mechanisms to track IP addresses and gather other information from website users. This information is used for system administration purposes and for analyzing how people use our website and how we can improve it. We may also use other technology, such as clear gifs, to gauge the effectiveness of our services and advertising. When you use a mobile device to connect to our website through a service provider that uniquely identifies your mobile device, we may receive that unique identifier and use it to offer extended services to you, which may require collection of your mobile phone number.

**_Sharing of Information_**

Except as set forth below, we will not release your name, mailing address, email address, phone numbers, or any other personal information to our advertisers or others without your consent.

If you choose to provide personal information for a limited purpose, such as a survey, your consent will be deemed given for the release of personal information for that purpose only.

Any information that you choose to share in public areas of this website, such as comments, becomes public when posted. You should not post any personal information that you wish to keep private.

We may use third-party contractors to perform certain services for us, such as hosting this website, sending email communications, and providing data analysis. We may provide your personal information to those contractors on a confidential basis when needed to perform their duties.

We may also disclose personal information in special cases, such as when we have reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing or threatening injury to us or a third party, or when we believe the law requires it, such as to comply with a court order, subpoena, or warrant. We also reserve the right to transfer or assign personal information in the event of a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or substantially all of our assets.

In addition, we may provide aggregate statistics about users, registered subscribers, online traffic patterns, and related information to our existing or potential sponsors or other reputable third parties, or in response to a government request; but those statistics will not personally identify you or any other visitor to our website.

**_How to Review Your Personal Information and to Opt-Out_**

You may contact us at the address set forth below if you wish to review, correct, or update any personal information that we may have about you, or if you wish to opt-out of receiving communications from us. You may also use the links on the bottom of our email messages to make changes to your email preferences.

**_Security of Information_**

We endeavor to safeguard the information we collect online. However, please remember that no transmission of data over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be completely secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. We will have no liability for disclosure of information obtained due to errors in transmissions or the unauthorized intervention of third parties.

Passwords may be used at our website to help protect your personal information. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your passwords and other access data. We recommend that you do not share your passwords with anyone, and that you notify us promptly if you believe your password security has been breached. If you are using a computer to which others have access, for example, in a computer lab, Internet cafe, or public library, always remember to log out and close your browser window when leaving our website.

Any personal information or sensitive data that you disclose through any discussion boards or other public online forums hosted on our website may be collected and used by others. We recommend caution when giving out personal information to others in these public online forums. When you choose to provide information on these forums, you do so at your own risk. The information you share may be viewed by any other user of the site.

Donations, purchases, and other financial transactions on this website are handled by established third-party banking, processing, and distribution institutions. Information relating to your financial transactions will not be stored on the servers for this website.

**_Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy_**

We never collect information at our website from persons we know to be under the age of 13. If we learn that personal information relating to someone under the age of 13 has been disclosed on our website, we will take appropriate steps to delete that information.

**_International Users_**

This website is hosted in the United States of America. By providing personal information to us, you are consenting to the transfer of your personal information to the United States and the use of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**_Changes to our Privacy Policy or Terms of Service_**

We may revise our Privacy Policy or other Terms of Service from time to time. We will post the changes on this website.

**_Questions about our Privacy Policy or Terms of Service_**

If you have questions about our Privacy Policy or other Terms of Service, you may contact us at:

**Delaware First Media**  
1200 N. DuPont Hwy.  
Dover, DE 19901  

_Effective as of August 31, 2012_
